

# **CONTACT**

•

+33 6 45 42 25 75



thibault.dilman@tuta.io



meysow.github.io/My-Portfolio



6 bis rue Sainte-Marie, 97410, Saint-Pierre, La Réunion

# **EDUCATION**

## 2015 - 2017:

Master in apprenticeship «Audit & Finance»,

IESEG School of Management & Société Générale

#### 2014 - 2015:

Bachelor, Dual Degree, Almaty Management University, Kazakhstan

## 2012 - 2017:

**IESEG School of Management** 

## 2011 - 2012:

Terminale S at Lycée Turgot

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- ⇒ Communication
- ⇒ Adaptability
- ⇒ Teamwork
- ⇒ Problem-solving

# **LANGUAGES**

- ⇒ English: Operational (TOEIC 940)
- ⇒ Spanish: Scholar level
- ⇒ Russian : Notions

# THIBAULT DILMAN

Web Developer

# INTRODUCTION

As an enthusiastic and driven Junior Developer, I have experience working with React, Next, and HTML/CSS. I pride myself on my work ethic and dedication to continuously improving my technical skills. For example, I recently completed a project where I developed a responsive website using React, which involved troubleshooting and finding innovative solutions. I am excited to bring my problem-solving skills and enthusiasm to a team where I can contribute to the organization's success while continuing to grow as a developer.

# Front-End Javascript Typescript HTML CSS/SASS React Js Next Js Other MongoDB Express Nongoose Nongoose Sanity Sanity Other

## **EXPERIENCE**

## 2021 - 2023: LIONBRIDGE, Web.

Search engine evaluator / Formation in Web Development.

- Conducted detailed analyses of search results to evaluate the relevance and accuracy of search algorithms.
- Utilized tools such as Google Analytics and Microsoft Excel to track and analyze search
- · Communicated findings and recommendations to the search engine team to improve the user experience.

### 2018 - 2020: PROPER TRADING, Market Finance.

Trader specialized on the DAX30 Futures Index (FDAX).

- Conducted extensive research and analysis to identify trends and make informed trading decisions.
- Utilized technical analysis tools and software to track market movements and identify trading opportunities.
- · Maintained a strong network of contacts in the financial industry, enabling me to stay informed about market news and trends.

# 2015 - 2017: SOCIETE GENERALE, Market Finance.

Sales assistant in cross-assets structured products in apprenticeship.

- · Relashionship Management: Customer & Intern (Trading, Middle & Back Office).
- Pricing of products & response to client's tenders.
- Executing orders on primary and secondary financial markets.
- · Termsheet editing & Booking of the products.
- Follow up & monitoring of financial products during their lifetime.

## **INTERESTS**

- Rock Climbing: Passionate about rock climbing and have traveled to various locations around the world, including Laos, the Canaries, Greece, Thailand, and La Réunion. Develops determination and problem-solving skills.
- Team Sports: Played volleyball for 4 years and football for 8 years, including participation in the Junior World Cup (Gothia Cup, Göteborg, Sweden) and tournament in Brazil. Demonstrates teamwork and communication skills.
- Scuba Diving: Certified at the CMAS level 1. Demonstrates a willingness to learn and explore new environments.
- Chess: Great interest in chess, enjoys analyzing strategy and problem-solving. Develops critical thinking skills.